like say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in Heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquity of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six day
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy manservant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill
Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor thou
shallal not covet thy neighbor's house
thou shallal not cover thy neighbor's
wife nor his man's servant nor his maid
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors I read
Exodus 20: 1-17 may the Lord add a
blessing to the reading of his word in
Jesus name we pray amen
amen amen so here on question and answer
you can ask us a question and we'll
answer it according to the King James
Bible and if we cannot find the answer
we will see further counsel to bring you
an answer at a later time keep in mind
that all vague questions would not be
answered and all long scripture
questions would not be answered for time
sake but we may be able to point you in
the direction of a DVD or CD that you
can purchase by calling office so please
be as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our ansers out of the King
James Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream and
you may begin to send in your questions
at this time even questions that pertain
the everlasting life we just asking that
you keep your scriptures to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
you the family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Jerome Grace and
peace Brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Dre good evening
brother James good evening everyone
sister Deborah good evening brother
Sean good
evening and we have the guest caller
with us and I'm brother Cornell sister
Deborah what is our first question of
the evening uh yes there are several
held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so uh Zion asks why can't
I find anywhere in the New Testament
where Jesus says anything about not
eating pork okay brother Dre so why is
that not found in the New Testament
scriptures about not eating pork let's
go over to uh Matthew the 13th chapter
we gonna answer that question Matthew 13
and we're gonna pick it up at verse 51
let's look at something Jesus said here
Matthew 13 51 and 52 when you get it
James go ahead and read it Jesus said
unto them have ye understood all these
things they say unto him yay Lord then
said he unto them therefore every scribe
which is instructed unto the Kingdom of
Heaven is like unto a man that is a
householder which bringeth forth out of
his treasure things new and old so we
going to look to the law and to the
testimony because if you don't speak
according to that word it is because
there is no light in you and you must do
that so let's go over to Isaiah 66 and
we gonna look at something that is going
to take place and then we're gon to look
at the same thing in the New Testament
Isaiah 66 and we're g to pick it up at
verse
15 Isaiah 66 and verse 15
go ahead brother for behold the Lord
will come with fire and with his
chariots like a whirlwind to render his
anger with Fury and his rebuke with
flames of
fire for by fire and by sword will the
Lord plead with All Flesh and the slain
of the Lord shall be many so we reading
about the coming of the Lord and the
Judgment that's going to take place at
his coming but let's see who who this is
talking about that he is going to judge
go ahead verse
17 they that sanctify themselves and
purify themselves in the gardens behind
one tree in the midst eating swine's
flesh and the Abomination and the mouse
shall be consumed together sayeth the
Lord notice this it
says Those Behind one tree in the midst
eating swine's flesh and the Abomination
and the mouse will be
consumed so here the swine is talking
about the pork and it says it ends it
with sayth the Lord now let's see who
this Lord is that saying that let's go
to Second
Thessalonians first
chapter 2 Thessalonians first chapter
and we gonna read verses s through
n Go ahead brother and to you who are
troubled rest with us when the Lord
Jesus shall be revealed from heaven with
his mighty angels in flaming fire taking
Vengeance on them that know not God and
that obey not the gospel of our Lord
Jesus Christ who shall be punished with
Everlasting destruction from the
presence of the Lord and from the glory
of his power so the Lord is coming to
judge the world and although you may not
read it here in the New Testament right
here it is bagged up in the old and we
must speak to the law and to the
testimony so I hope that that
helps that's is it that's it for me
right now yes sir and be nice if they
knew that he's the one that gave the
dietary law absolutely brother all right
thank you for that brother as we move on
to our next question next question
Israel tribe asked where is it in
scripture where God says
always pray to the east so in the
scriptures brother Julius do it say
always pray to the
east no that that's not written in
scripture always pray to the east let's
go the one example where he an example
of praying toward the spot where the
Lord said the temple stood
let's go to 2 Chronicles quickly brother
James I'm there 2 Chronicles
7 2 Chronicles 7 and please begin
reading read verse 14- 16 when you get
it go
ahead if my people which are called by
my name shall humble themselves and pray
and seek my face and turn from their
Wicked Ways then will I hear from heaven
and will forgive their sin and will heal
their land so he's telling you if when
the people pray
continue now mine eyes shall be open and
mine ears attent unto the prayer that is
made in this place yes for now have I
Chosen and Sanctified this house that my
name may be there forever and my eyes
and my heart shall be there perpetually
that is the spot on where the temple
once stood it's not there no more it's
not there no more it was torn down so
now he never told you to pray to he said
my heart and my eyes will be on this
spot okay so now but we pray because we
in the west we pray toward that way on
the spot where it stood at not always
not he didn't tell you always pray to
the east another spot let's go to uh and
case in point Jonah chapter one The Book
of Jonah chapter
1 Jonah 1 and we going to read verse 17
to show you you don't need to pray to
the east the Lord can hear you from
anywhere Jonah 1 and
17 when you get it read it James now the
Lord had prepared a great fish to
swallow up Jonah and Jonah was in the
belly of the fish three days and three
nights chapter two verse one Jonah 2 and
one read then Jonah prayed unto the Lord
his God out of the fish's belly now you
could read the rest of it on your own he
just Jonah didn't know where the fish
was
but he prayed out of the spot out of the
fish's belly my last place and it's
short Luke
11 Luke 11 okay and read Luke 11 read
verse one and two and I'm
done and it came to pass that as he was
praying in a certain place when he
ceased one of his disciples said unto
him Lord teach us to pray as John also
taught his disciples
his disciples said teach us to pray and
look what Jesus said go ahead and he
said unto them when ye pray say Our
Father which art in Heaven that's good
James that's good there's no Direction
given he just said when you pray you say
Our Father which are in
heaven that's all I got anybody want to
add to
that yeah I got one more add to
it Go Psalms chapter
and read verse seven what
chapter
five and verse
7 okay Psalm 5 and verse 7 says but as
for me I will come into thine house in
the multitude of thy mercy and in thy
fear will I worship toward Theo thy Holy
Temple okay it's one of the reasons but
if if you uh in Russia then you wouldn't
be facing the uh uh uh East you'd be
facing the West right if you was in
France you wouldn't be facing the East
you'd be facing the
South and if you was in Egypt You' be
facing the
north there's there's nothing about East
is where the temple is located because
like julus read earlier God say his eyes
and his ears will be always will always
be on that spot what we doing is just
trying to H the bed a little bit all I
have to say Amen thank you
gu hope that answered your question as
we move on to our next moving on uh
micia CER have two questions he says if
it only States and the evening and the
morning were the first day how do we
know that day was a Sunday and his
second question is if I'm married to a
gentile am I in
sin all right guess
caller first thing is let's go and read
the uh
uh a couple of days let's start at
Genesis
1 and read verse
31 Genesis 1 and verse
31 and God s and God saw everything that
he had made and behold it was very good
and the evening and the morning were the
sixth
day okay go to Genesis 2 and verse
one thus the heavens and the Earth were
finished and all the host of them go
ahead and on the seventh day God ended
his work which he had made and he rested
on the seventh day from all his work
which he had made
now that seventh day was the last day of
the week which God Called It Sabbath day
they called it the Sabbath day now the
first day that the evening the morning
is the first day of the week which man
named it
Sunday that's the day they uh uh decided
that they was going to worship the son
so now and you look at your calendar and
you'll see that Sunday is the first day
as far as the uh second uh uh question
is about uh uh uh being Mar to the
Gentiles is he in sin let's go to First
John the thir chapter and read verse
four first John the 3 chapter and verse
4 whosoever committes sin transgresseth
also the law for sin is the transgress
of the
law that's what saying is the
transgression of the law that's all they
have to
say all right we'll leave it right there
hope that answers your question as we
move on to our next question next
question was Jesus and John
cousins Jerome was Jesus and John
cousins well according to the flesh um
they were related because they parents
were related according to the flesh
let's go to uh Luke 2 verse 34 and
36 Luke 2 vers
34 and 36 through 36 through 36 and
Simon blessed them and said unto Mary
his mother behold this child is set for
the fall and Rising again of many in
Israel and for a sign which shall be
spoken against yay a sword shall pierce
through thine own soul also that the
thoughts of that chapter one I'm sorry
yeah okay chapter one not two okay sorry
about that that's okay chapter 1 through
36 yeah okay then said Mary unto the
angel how shall this be seeing I know
not a man and the angel answered and
said unto her the Holy Ghost shall come
upon thee and the power of the highest
shall overthrow thee therefore also that
Holy thing which shall be born of thee
shall be called The Son of God and
behold thy cousin Elizabeth she has also
conceived a son in her old age and this
is the sixth month with her who was also
called Baron yeah so Elizabeth was
John's mother and she was cousin to Mary
um um Jesus mother according to the
flesh so they were
related that's all I got
on all right thank you for that hope
that answer their question as we move on
to our next question next question be
alert as is the earth flat does
Scripture show any
evidence no the Earth is not flat and
the scripture don't bag up any evidence
saying that it is flat let's go um to
job the 26th chapter job
26 okay because they do have shots of
the earth you know uh from the
satellites from out in space and things
that that nature and everything that we
see pertaining to the Earth is
spherical which is like a circle just
like the Globes you see in the stores
when you see Globes all the time they
are r
job
206 and read that one verse 7 for
me he stretches out the north over the
empty place and hangeth the Earth upon
nothing all right so this is the Lord to
say stretches out the Earth over the
empty place and hey and hangeth the
Earth upon nothing so this is the same
Lord that we F to read about in Isaiah
40 go to Isaiah 40 I'm there
when you get to Isaiah 40 brother pick
it up at that verse one and then we're
going to uh do some skipping there
Isaiah
40 and read verse one for me go ahead
Comfort ye Comfort ye my people saith
your God all right skip down because
it's the same one that say he hung the
Earth out there on nothing and when you
see the space shots it don't look like a
Rubik's Cube it don't look like a box it
look like a circle that's hanging out
there verse 12 let's read about some
more what he
did who has measured the waters in the
hollow of his hand and met it out heaven
with the span and comprehended the dust
of the Earth in a measure and weigh the
mountains in scales and the hills in a
balance yes that's one bad God ain't it
Jame yes sir turn over and read 21 and
22 for me and that'll be it because this
God that did all this let's see what
else he had to say go ahead have ye not
known have ye not heard have it not been
told you from the beginning have you not
understood from the foundations of the
earth it is he that sth upon the circle
of the earth and the inhabitants thereof
are as grasshoppers that stretcheth out
the heavens as a curtain and spreaded
them out as a tent to dwell in so this
is the Lord saying that talking about
himself he say it is he himself that sth
upon the circle of the earth so the
Earth is not flat it is a circle it's
spiral as in round and that's what the
book bags up and that's what we have to
say about that and I hope that that was
able to shed some light for
you cordel can we go back to that job
22 job 22 and read verse 12 and 14
because you said that the scripture said
that he sth upon the circle that's c i r
or c l
e job 22 and read verse 12
James it is not it or is not God in the
height of heaven and behold the height
of the Stars how high they are verse 14
thick clouds are a covering to him that
he seeth not and he walketh in the
circuit of Heaven there's that circuit
again c i and the definition of circuit
is the act of moving or P or being
encircled all right Earth is
round okay so we hope to be able to put
that to rest about the Earth being flat
because all those other people would
have fell off a long time
ago all right hope that answered your
question next question next question
most love says I recently got baptized
in jesus' name with one of the iog
churches why didn't I feel like I felt
when I got baptized in the Sunday church
I cried but not this
time okay Julius can you explain that
question I can't explain why she didn't
why she didn't cry when she got baptized
in the Israel of God you know it's not
written anywhere where you supposed to
cry when you get baptized you know most
people that get baptized that I've seen
and witness they are uh they cry when
they came into the knowledge of the
truth they found out about the real
Jesus and they rejoice in that and uh
the so I don't know if you just
emotional but the great emotional coming
to the truth is enough to make you shout
uh but the only script I can help you
out with is acts let's go to acts the
10th chapter
and I hope this helps
okay cuz if I get in that water and and
come up out of that water meaning that
my past sins are forgiven me that is
enough to cry and Shout
about acts 10 acts 10 and pick it up at
uh at verse 44 let's get right to the
point while Peter Cornelius go ahead
while Peter yet spake these words the
Holy Ghost fell on all them which heard
the
word go ahead and they of the
circumcision which believe were
astonished as many as came with Peter
because that on the Gentiles also was
poured out the gift of the Holy Ghost
and then at verse 47 and this is it what
did he say can any man forbid water that
these should not be baptized which have
received the Holy Ghost as well as we so
the Gentiles got baptized and I'm sure
the they was they were they
rejoiced they rejoiced because now also
upon the Gentiles where the go the word
of God given so that they too might
obtain salvation and that is enough to
shout and cry about that's all I got yes
sir indeed uh let's go to acts two and
just read one verse two acts two and
read that verse
41 because we hope that this is how you
feel at least yeah Acts 2 and 41 because
to find a true and living God is like
you said brother Julius is really past
finding out
words 2 and 41 go ahead then they that
gladly received his word were baptized
and the same day there were added unto
them about 3,000 Souls yep so we hoped
you had some Joy too don't we Julius
that's right yes hope I was baptized
when I was a child
and I and I know I didn't know what was
going on I know I was baptized under the
wrong
Jesus
yeah all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
moving on I am is I am Israel ask if a
person's spouse commits spiritual
fornication such as C reading devation
and won't repent is that an example of
what Jesus meant when he spoke of
divorce I know what physical F uh
fornication
is brother Dre what you say well let's
go read that let's go to uh Matthew
19 um and we gonna read verse three no
that's not what that's talking about
however you know when we were in our
land the Lord had some judgments on
people that did such things and you can
read about that on your own in
Deuteronomy 13 but for now we just going
to read Matthew uh 19 and read verse
three brother and we'll
skip the Pharisees also came unto him
tempting him and saying unto him is it
lawful for a man to put away his wife
for every cause read verse eight and
nine he saith unto them
Moses because of the hardness of your
hearts suffered you to put away your
wies but from the beginning it was not
so and I say unto you whosoever shall
put away his wife except it be for
fornication and shall marry another
committeth adultery and whosoever
marrieth her is put away is which is put
away doeth commit adultery this is
talking about physical adultery not
spiritual
adultery okay so I hope that that helps
but you could read that Deuteronomy 13
on your own and that will help you as
well that's all I
got don't forget to pray right Dre that
he's right yeah all right hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next question next question Valencia
Wars you to explain deuteron omy 29
ver8 why only half of the tribe of
manasse can you
explain all right let's go there brother
James at Deuteronomy 29 I'm there and
read that verse eight and the guess
carer would take it from
there 29 and Deuteronomy 29 and8 and we
took their land and gave it for an
inheritance unto the reubenites and to
the gadites and to the half tribe of
manasse okay way it sound it look like
it gave that that manasse had a whole
tribe but no let me show you what it
mean first thing is let's go and see uh
how many sons that Jacob had and what
was their name let's go into Exodus the
1 chapter and read verses
1-5 Exodus 1 and vers 1 through
now these are the names of the children
of Israel which came into Egypt every
man in his household came with Jacob
Reuben Simeon Levi and Judah isachar
Zebulon and Benjamin Dan and Nepali Gad
and Asher and all the souls that came
out of the loins of Jacob were 70 souls
for Joseph was in Egypt
already now if you count all of them
Sons you named 12 sons and you didn't
see the name Manassa nowhere in there no
sir so what is it talking about because
Joseph had two sons let's go in the uh
uh Genesis the 48th
chapter and read verse
one Genesis 48 and verse one says and it
came to pass after these things that one
told Joseph Behold thy father is sick
and he took with him his two sons
manasse and
Ephraim now so Joseph had two sons so
but it was the tribe of
Joseph
so and and and manasse was just a half
of the tribe of Joseph and Ephraim was
the other half of the tribe of
Joseph so it should have been so so what
they saying is you know the half tribe
which is uh uh uh the half tribe which
which is uh which which is Ephraim was
the one that was given because Ephraim
is the half
tribe I'm sorry it should have it should
have said that
Manasseh which is the half tribe of
Joseph because manasse is only half of
Joseph which is one of the 12 12 Tribes
of deob so all it meant was it just
manasse it was given to one of man one
of Joseph's Sons which was just a half
of a
tribe or the whole tribe was
Joseph that's all I have to say yeah all
right thank you for that hope that
answer that question as we move on with
the time check yes the time is
uh
8:00 Clarence Jones says in Genesis 6
verse 2 and verse
4 people say this was angels having sex
with women and they made Giants is this
true and can you
explain ain't no truth in that but let's
go to Genesis
6 Genesis 6 and when you get there
brother read that two and four and the
guest caller would take it from there
Genesis 6 and 2 and verse four that the
sons of God saw the daughters of men
that they were fair and they took them
wives of all which they chose verse four
there were giants in the earth in those
days and also after that when the sons
of God came in unto the daughters of men
and they be children to to them the same
became Mighty Men which were of old men
of
renown but the first thing years there
was
Giants on this side of the fluid too
that mean once the Lord drowned the
whole earth and save Noah and his
children still there with Giants on this
side of the earth you know that's that's
a that's what what goliath was the son
of Enoch in fact there's a lot of Giants
on this side of the world
but what we but what they saying about
the sons of God which they are calling
which they think of angels looked upon
the daughters of men and and took them
wine first thing is they are two sets of
sons of God and one set of the Angels
job talks about them but also there's
another another Son of God a set of sons
of God and we going to
use and and we going to use the
scripture to point them out first thing
is let's go into Luke the 3 chapter
we're GNA start with Jesus and we're
going to do a little lineage right in
here okay Luke 3 and we're going to read
23 and
24 then we're going to
skip okay Luke 323 and verse
24 and Jesus himself begin to began to
be about 30 years of age being as was
supposed the son of Joseph which was the
son of heli which was the son of matat
which was the son of Levi which was the
son of melchi which was the son of Janna
which was the son of
Joseph now skip down to verse 34 we're
going to continue this lineage go ahead
which was the son of Jacob which was the
son of Isaac which was the son of Abra
which was the son of Tara which was the
son of nikor which was the son of sarak
which was the son of ragath which was
the son of filac which was the son of
hear which was the son of Salah which
was the son of Canan which was the son
of aparat aidad which was the son of sim
which was the son of no which was the
son of lamech which was the son of
Methuselah which was the son of Enoch
which was the son of Jared which was the
son of melel which was the son of Canan
which was the son of Enos which was the
son of Seth which was the son of Adam
which was the son of
God now all the people that all these
lineage all of these was the sons of God
but then so who was where the son of uh
the the da the men come from it came
from Cain because God disinherited Cain
let's let's go to Genesis the 4th
chapter and uh read verses 9- 11 skip
down and read 13 and
14 11 and verse 13 and 14 so Genesis 4
veres 9-1 says and the Lord said unto
Cain where is Abel thy brother and he
said I know not am I My Brother's Keeper
and he said what has thou done the voice
of thy brother's blood crith unto me
from the ground and now art thou curs
from the earth which ha opened her mouth
to receive thy brother's blood from
thine
hand down God curs disinherit him 13 and
and Cain said unto the Lord my
punishment is greater than I can bear
behold thou has driven me out this day
from the face of the Earth and from thy
face shall I be hid and I shall be a
fugitive and a vagabond in the earth and
it shall come to pass that everyone that
findeth me shall slay
me now so the Lord disinherited Cain and
and he didn't even have Cain in in the
lineage of the sons of God so let's go
into Genesis the 5th chapter and we
going to read 1
through6 okay Genesis 5:
1-6 this is the book of the generations
of Adam in that day that God created man
in the likeness of God made he him male
and female created he them and blessed
them and called their name Adam in the
day which they were created and Adam
lived 130 years and begot a son in his
own likeness after his after his image
and he called his name
Seth and the days after or I'm sorry and
the days of Adam after he had begotten
Seth were 800 years and he begot sons
and daughters and all the days that Adam
lived were 930 years and he died and
Seth lived 100
5 years and begat
Enos now if you run that lineage on down
to
Noah and across the flood you will not
see any one that come out of Cain
because the Lord dis
in so now so and that that that linage
run clean on down to Jesus just like we
read Jesus and we back it up back to
Adam which is the Son of God so all the
people that didn't uh s that uh didn't
uh uh uh go the way of Cain that didn't
come out out of Cain was called the sons
of God all of
them so now as
for the daughters of uh uh Beth you know
also Adam too because Adam had other
sons and sons and daughter the daughters
of Seth and Adam looked up the sons
brother of Seth and Adam looked up on
the daughters of Cain and start to
Mar you they see that these guys God
marrying these daughters then the Lord
said my spirit is not going to always
strive with man because he knew that it
was going to be a problem yeah these are
these are these sons of God is talking
about the Adam seed by way of set thr
down to Jesus so now as far as the
angels are concerned they are also
called sons of man of God but let's see
if they marry anybody go to Matthews the
22nd chapter and read verse 29 and
30 Matthew
22 and vers 29 and
say Jesus answered and said unto them ye
do he not knowing the scriptures nor nor
the power of God for in the resurrection
they neither marry nor are given in
marriage but are as the angels of God in
heaven now because the thing about it is
there was a custom in Israel if a man
had a wife and he died and didn't have
no children by her his brother had to
marry her and they said well look there
were seven brothers and none of them had
children by her through all the marri
one man dying then his this brother
married her and then that brother
married her So eventually the woman died
so whose wife is she in the resurrection
and that's what he said look say look in
the resurrection they neither marry nor
give in
marriage but
they like the angels of heaven so the
angels Don't marry they don't give it
marriage two species you got a spirit
men and the flesh and blood men they
can't make babies and angels Don't marry
that's why you ain't never seen a baby
angel once again too the Lord said every
seed after his own kind if an
angel and blood woman and had a child
that mean that there was an angel the
child was an angel and he couldn't die
we see every one of them right here
today all them Giants but the Bible
didn't say that the Giants came out of
them it just said there was Giants in
the
land and Matthew it angels Don't marry
not giving marriage so the sons of God
looked upon the dogs of men and took
them to wi with the sons of Adam F and
all through that lineage looked up on
the daughters of
Cain and they was fair and they start
marrying Chain's
daughters both sets of Flesh and Blood
that's
all all right thank you for that hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next next one one Mona wants
to know how to stop people from saying
oh she or he was here
before Julius he or she was here before
how do you put a stop to that I was
trying to figure out the context of the
question are they talking about a
resurrection are they talking about uh
they died and were resuscitated or or
are they talking about um coming in
another body in another form well
whatever it is the phenomenon is in the
French called
deju deju the definition of Day Z Vu is
the false sense of feeling that you
already experienced something be
something before even though you know
you haven't 97% of the people says man I
feel like I've been there I feel like
I've done this before I feel like I've
been here before it's a it is a false
sense
of security and lack of understanding
nobody's been here before except this
one right here let's go to St John the
17th chapter this is how you stop people
when they say I've been here before
unless you physically went home and came
back home that's the only understanding
I can get out of it
but look what look what Jesus said when
he prayed to his father this is the only
one that's been here before in the
context that I think that you're trying
to say St John
17 and read verse 5 Look what Jesus said
to the father go ahead and now oh Father
glorify thou me with thine own self with
the glory which I had with thee before
the world was so he was with the father
in the beginning came down in this in an
occupied of Flesh and Blood body
occupied for 33 and a half years was
crucified stayed in the grave three days
and three nights resurrected came down
for for 40 days and went back and sat on
the right hand of the father he is the
only one that's been here before that's
all I got y let that's
it something else in there yes let's go
go to St John the 6th chapter and start
reading at verse
38 than John 6 John 6 and verse
38 he says for I came down from heaven
not to do mine own will but the will of
him that sent
me and he he and this is the Father's
will which has sent me that of all which
he ha given me I should lose nothing but
should raise it up again at the last
day is the last day here no sir no
sir y I'm sorry and this is the will of
him that sent me that everyone which
seeth the son and believeth on him may
have everlasting life and I will raise
him up at the last
day Skip down and read verse
44 no man can come to me except the
Father which has sent me draw him and I
will raise him up at the last
day read verse
54 whosoever eateth My Flesh and
drinketh my blood ha eternal life and I
will raise him up at the last
day so the last day is not here so
whoever died is
still and he will not come back until
the last
day that mean whoever telling like that
they just running their
mouth all right hope that answerers your
question as we continue to move on
continue to move on no is tap says why
can't the soul mentioned in Matthew 10
verse 28 be killed by them men if it is
a body Flesh and
Blood all right Jerome why is
that uh let's go read the verse that's
given Matthews 10 and 28 I'm
there go ahead bro and fear not them
which kill the body but are not able to
kill the soul but rather fear him which
is able to destroy both soul and Body in
hell yeah so a lot of people get
confused when they read that verse
that's why it says in the in the Bible
um you have a more sure word of Prophecy
you you get confused in what you reading
in the New Testament is telling you to
go to the old Testament it's a more sure
word okay so let's let's do that let's
go to um 1 Samuel chapter 23 I wanted to
show you um
Saul who was so jealous and envy so
David want to kill him and then I'm
going to show you a verse where David
uses a term associated with what we read
in this verse
okay 1 Samuel 2 3 read verse 15 just
verse
15 and David saw that Saul was come out
to seek his life and David was in the
wilderness of Ze in the
wood seeking his seeking his life
because he want to kill them okay so we
going to establish whether you refer to
it as a soul or
body okay Saul wanted to kill David's
Soul or body okay so go to the 24 4
chapter and read verse 11 24 verse 11
moreover my father see yeay see the
skirt of thy robe in my hand for in that
I cut off the skirt of thy robe and
killed thee not know thou and see that
there is neither evil nor transgression
in my hand and I have not sinned against
thee yet thou hunst my soul to take it
yeah he hunted his soul to take it cuz
he want to kill him kill what his soul
or kill his body it's the same thing
okay so yeah that verse is confusing but
that nail in the wall is your soul and
your body is one and the same you know
even though that verse is confusing
that's your nail in the wall okay uh
let's go to Isaiah 51 and verse 23 to
kind of establish that point a little
further Isaiah 51
verse 23 Isaiah 51 and 23 says but I
will put it into thine hand I'm sorry
but I will put it into the hand of them
that afflict thee which have said to thy
Soul bow down that we may go over and
thou has laid thy body as the ground and
as the street to them that went over
yeah so he said thy
Soul lay down that we may go over and
what he laid down was his body cuz the
body and the soul is one and the same
that's all I got
on can I throw something in yes yes
sir look
Matthews was there and he wrote for he
he heard the same speech yeah that
Luke
okay now let's let's go and see what
Luke said about that same speech that
Jesus made let's go into Luke the 12th
chapter and we're going to read verses
four and
five okay Luke 12: 4 and 5 and I say
unto you my friends be not afraid of
them that kill the body and after that
have no more that they can do but I will
forewarn you whom ye shall fear fear Him
which after Heath killed have power to
cast into hell yay I say unto you fear
Him Now both of them heard the same
speech he didn't say nothing about uh
Soul did
he the exact same speech one of the
place let's go into Ezekiel 18th
chapter Ezekiel
uhhuh not in verse one
verse one the word of the Lord came unto
me again saying what mean ye that you
use this proverb concerning the land of
Israel saying the fathers have eaten
sour grapes and the children's teeth are
set on
edge as I live sayth as I live sayeth
the Lord God ye shall not have occasion
anymore to use this proverb in Israel
behold All Souls are mine as the soul of
the father so also the soul of the son
is mine the soul that sth it shall
die that's simple isn't it y soul is s
it it shall die because body is the soul
Genesis 7 chapter say God breathe unto
man's nost he became a living Soul First
Corinthians the 15th chapter will tell
you the first man Adam was made a living
Soul so that confusing statement that
Matthews wrote but Luke wrote it clear
that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question there we move on to our next
question next question King juu J Judah
asks was the most high still divorced to
Israel during the time of the Messiah in
the New Testament
all right was the most high still
divorced to Israel during the time of
the Messiah in the New Testament gu call
them
yes Israel was he still the was still
divorce from
Israel Let's Go and show you when the
Lord bring Israel back he going to take
Israel Into the
Wilderness and let's look
at what's going to happen let's go into
Jose the second
chapter we're going to read verses 14-
16 and Skip down and read 19 to
20 okay that was Jose
4 Jose 2 oh Jose 2 sorry about that Jose
2 14- 16 verse okay 14- 16 therefore
behold I will Allure her and bring her
into the Wilderness and speak
comfortably unto her and I will give her
her Vineyard from then in the valley of
acor for a Door of Hope and she shall
sing there as in the days of her Youth
and as in the day which she came up out
of the land of Egypt and it shall be at
that day sayith the Lord that thou shalt
call me ishai and shalt call me no more
baa
okay the word isi means my
husband so you gonna call me my husband
in that day when I return you now skip
down to verse 19 and and read 19 and 20
and I will betro thee unto me forever
yay I will betro
thee in the Bible in this particular
case mean I will marry you
okay beat it again just with the
understanding that the betol right here
the Lord is talking about Mary Now read
it again 19 and 20 and I will betro thee
unto me forever yay I will betroth thee
unto me in righteousness and in judgment
and in loving kindness and in mercies
and I will even betroth thee unto unto
me in faithfulness and thou shalt know
the
Lord now that's right when he bring
Israel H back the acts of the marriage
starts in the wilderness but it
continues let's go into Revelation the
19th
Chapter and we're going to read verses
[Music]
7-9 Revelation
19 vers 7-9 says let us be glad and
rejoice and give honor to him for the
marriage of the Lamb is come and his
wife ha made herself ready and to her
was granted that she should be arrayed
in fine linen clean and white for the
fine linen is the righteousness of
saints and he said unto me write blessed
are they which are called unto the
marriage supper of the lamb and he saith
unto me these are the true sayings of
God so he is not going to marry Israel
until he returned so right now he is
still
divorced from
Israel that's
all all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on ah asked in Luke 23 verse 43
when Jesus tells him that he'll be with
him in Paradise what does that mean if
no one has been to Heaven All right we
talking about the thief here but that is
correct no one has been to Heaven except
for he that came down which is the Lord
that we read about earlier but when he
told him that he would be with him in
Paradise that's when Jesus Come into his
own
kingdom for thousand years he GNA be
sitting on his throne but let's go into
that uh Luke
23 Luke 23 I'm there and let's just pick
up a little Story start at 39 and read
down for me go ahead
and one of the Mal factors which were
hang railed on him saying if thou be
Christ save thyself and us but the other
answering rebuked him saying doest not
thou fear God seeing Thou Art in the
same condemnation so this other one here
is the one that asks the Lord can he be
with him in Paradise go ahead 41 and we
indeed justly for we receive the due
reward of our Deeds but this man had
done nothing amiss and he said unto
Jesus Lord remember me when thou comest
into thy kingdom so this thief here has
some knowledge he knew that Jesus was
going to have a kingdom which he also
call his rest which he also call His
Thousand Years of Peace which he also
said that our hard-headed forefathers
and for mothers won't be there who
didn't make the cut read that verse 4 3
and Jesus said unto him verily I say
unto thee today shalt thou be with me in
Paradise so he was just making him a
promise telling him that today in the
future when I come into my kingdom I'm
telling you that you will be there with
me so this guy here has some knowledge
too let's go to um Isaiah 14 right quick
Isaiah 14 and let's see what is
let's see what uh it's going to be like
when Jesus Come into his
kingdom okay Isaiah 14 when you get
there brother just read that verse one
and then we're going to skip down Isaiah
14 and one because it's going to be a
lot of different people there from
different races this this show is for
whosoever will let them come and serve
God go ahead for the Lord will have
mercy on Jacob and will yet choose
Israel and set them in their own land
and the strangers shall be joined with
them and they shall cleave to the house
of Jacob yeah now this is everybody
there who made the cut they're going to
be there not just Israel read that verse
uh seven for me what is the earth going
to be like when Jesus sitting on his
kingdom the whole earth is at rest and
is quiet they they break forth into
singing yeah so this is when he is on
his throne it's going to be a beautiful
time and that Thief who ask to be in
Paradise he's going to be there also now
turn quickly to first Thessalonians
first
Thessalonians the fourth
chapter because the
Lord that first resurrection is where
everybody that made the cut is going to
be and the living they'll still be
around but the ones that have died or
the ones that make the cut they're going
to meet the Lord in the clouds 1
Thessalonians 4 and pick it up at there
verse 14 when you get there brother go
ahead for if we believe that Jesus died
and rose again even so them also which
sleep in Jesus will bring will I'm sorry
will God bring with him that's what that
Thief Knew Too that hey the Lord was
going to be sitting on a throne go ahead
for this we say unto you by the word of
the Lord that we which are alive and
remain unto the coming of the Lord shall
not prevent them which are asleep uhhuh
for the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout with the voice of
the arch angel and with the Trump of God
and the dead in Christ shall rise first
yes it's that first resurrection that
thief of me there go ahead
then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air and
so shall we ever be with the Lord and
come right back down to the earth and
the Lord is going to straighten it out
and take it by force and straighten it
out and he going to be on his throne and
the whole earth will be singing like all
that good stuff and the thief will be
there too in paradise and hope to see us
all there also that's all I
got I just want to throw in one more yes
sir First Corinth 15th
chapter vers 20 and
21 1 Corinthians 15 and verses 20 and TW
20 and 21 or through 23 okay but now is
Christ risen from the dead and become
the first fruits of them that slept
for Since By Man Came Death by man came
also the resurrection of the Dead for as
in Adam all die even so in Christ shall
all be made alive but every man in his
own order Christ the first fruits
afterward they that are Christ at his
coming do that if that Thief he repented
on the last day of his life he asked the
Lord remember him when he come into his
kingdom okay and Jesus Promised You I'm
going to do that but then according to
this he can't come until Jesus return
can he Christ and is coming Jesus is not
he therefore the thief is in the grave
ain't it
right that's all I wanted to say because
people always mess that up because the
punctuation is messed up because Jesus
saying to that Thief I'm promising you
today
that you will be with me be with me when
I when I come when I return yeah so
today day that he made the promise to
the thief right he if he saying that the
thief GNA be with him that day then
Jesus lied because Jesus didn't go uh
raised until three days later did
he that's all I have to say yes that
that need to be said to clear that up
about the thief going to
heaven
yeah all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on to the next one Lord have
mercy says the story of Samson is such a
bizarre illogical story to wrap my head
around please help me make sense of it
all right well if you like the Lord to
have some mercy use some Kinder words
next time and just say you don't
understand understand because the word
the Sam word of Samson is not bizarre
it's not odd and it's not illogical or
senseless so uh brother Julius can you
share some knowledge on that yes let's
go to HEB uh Hebrews the 11th chapter
brother James and while we turning there
uh she said the story of Samson is such
a bizarre El logical what's illogical
and what's bizarre
Samson was a real person Delilah was a
real person the Philistines were real
people it's written in the scripture and
the and the the book say it's impossible
for God to lie the only thing that could
be illogical or bizarre is if you don't
believe it that that means that if you
don't believe anything if you don't
believe in uh that means anything can be
a logical or
bizar this is what I got hope I hope
this help no offense intended but you
have to believe this book Because all
these things were written for our admin
Hebrews 11 and verse 6 Hebrew 11 and
verse 6 says but without faith it is
impossible to please him for he that
cometh to God must believe that he is
and that is he he is a rewarder of them
that diligently seek him so this Bible
was not written in vain is the word of
God it is the mind of God and in keeping
with obedience to it will lead you to uh
uh eternal life salvation there's
nothing illogical or hard to understand
about that the the the bottom the
question is do you believe this Bible
and the thing that's written in
it Samson disobeyed Samson disobeyed God
the woman cut his hair and he paid the
price for it that's the theme of the
story that's all I got I hope that
helped no no offense intended but the
bottom line is you have to believe this
right here it's not nothing in the Bible
is in iCal nothing it all makes sense
that's all I got brother cordal yeah yes
sir thank you for that and we hope that
you'll stay tuned with us so that we'll
be able to help you on some of those
other things also that you may not
understand prise God all right sister
Deborah I believe uh we going into new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for Wednesday November the 20th
2024 Jalia says I asked someone to show
me where the Bible mentions the Rapture
I was directed to 1 Thessalonians 4 vers
15-1 17 I showed them that he was
descending in verse 16 on his way to
Earth is there
another D what you say yeah Cornell just
read and yes Thessalonians 4 and 16 that
they shall that he is descending they
are ascending but where do they go from
there let's go to Zechariah
14 zeah 14 and we gonna start at verse
one and Skip to
three Zechariah 14 verse one and then
skip to three yes sir go ahead behold
the day of the Lord cometh and thy spoil
shall be divided in the midst of thee
yes sir go ahead then shall the Lord go
forth and fight against those Nations as
when he fought in the day of battle so
the Lord is gonna come down and he's
going to deal with these nations and he
is th us he is he is descending and we
are ascending but he said he's coming
down and where is he coming to go ahead
and his feet shall stand in that day
upon the Mount of Olives which is before
Jerusalem on the East and the Mount of
Olives shall cleave in the midst thereof
toward the East and toward the west and
there shall be a very great valley and
half of the mountain shall be shall
remove toward the North and half of it
toward the South now it says his feet
shall stand in that day on the Mount of
Olives so that means he is D he is he
descended we ascended we met him he came
down now where are the Saints that verse
five go ahead and ye shall flee to the
Valley of the mountains for the Valley
of the mountains shall reach unto AEL
yay ye shall flee like as ye fled from
before the earthquake in the days of
Uzziah king of Judah and the L and the
Lord my God shall come and all the
saints with the so the Lord is coming he
descended we ascended and met him and he
came and his feet stood on the Mount of
Olives and he came and all the saints
with him we got raptured off to Heaven
that is a bad teaching
please you know I I get you trying to
persuade somebody but yes that's
terrible and this is another bir
that deals with that I hope that
helps that's right brother D yeah J read
oh guest caller let me throw in the
words of a great Saint all right is
Jo let's go into job the 19th Chapter
let me show you what this great Saint
said we're going to start reading at
verse 23 to
26 to 27
job 19 and
23-27 oh that my words were now written
oh that they were printed in a book that
they were Graven with an iron pen and
led in the rock forever for I know that
my redeemer liveth and that he shall
stand at the latter day upon the Earth
and thou
stand shall stand at the latter day upon
the
earth oh so that's that's when his feet
hit Mount of Olives is that correct keep
reading and Thou after my skin worms
destroy this body yet and my
flesh and though and
though after my skin worms destroy this
body yet in my flesh shall I see God
whom I shall see for myself and my eyes
shall be hold and not another though my
Reigns be consumed within
me okay so where is it going to see him
at on Earth is that correct corre like
just just like the brother read in
Zechariah 14th chapter speaking will
standing that day on the Mount of ol and
if he had skipped down to verse n he
would have told you and the God shall be
king over all the Earth so there was no
Rapture there was a meeting that's all I
have to say
yep all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next
question next one The Air I Breathe as
is any type of addic addiction a form of
idolatry yeah it can be I mean U the
definition of idolatry is an object or a
person of extreme devotion an impostor a
pretender a false god hey it can be
things that aren't good for you that you
just refuse to give
up to be a Doctrine it could be a lot of
things anything you put in the head of
God can be an idol to
you so um let's go let's go to Isaiah 44
Isaiah
44 and you ask about addiction because
you've had some people that you know I
knew somebody had a house full of babies
has seven kids and um he let his
addiction take his job his house and all
that stuff he put that stuff up as an
idol he just couldn't quit weakness also
can be down letting Isaiah 44 pick it up
at verse
6 thus sayith the Lord the king of
Israel and his Redeemer the Lord of
hosts I am the first and I am the last
and beside me there is no God so if he's
the only God they got all that power
that's only one we need right James
that's right skip down read nine and
10 they that make a Graven image are all
of them vanity and their delectable
things shall not profit and they are
their own Witnesses they see not nor
know that they may be ashamed the Lord
say that even sometime when you make a
Graven image you know or something
delectable something that's very highly
pleasing to you but the ways there in
could be deaf or could create a big
problem for you verse 10 who has formed
a God or molten a Graven image that is
profitable for nothing nobody has formed
a God that was able to help them in any
kind of way except for the true and
living God and that's all I got on that
anybody else like
to all right hope that answered your
question there sister deorah time check
as we keep moving yes the time is
8:43 daughter of Judah
says many believe the law was done away
with when Christ was
sacrificed so now Matthew
22: 36-40
in John
14: 15-
25 are the only laws and those are in
quotation mark we now have to follow am
I correct in saying that Matthew 22
verse 36- 40 refers back to the Ten
Commandments with the first five showing
how to love God in the second F five
showing us how to love our neighbors
brother Dre to many that believe that
the law was done away with can you
please shed some light yeah the law is
not done away with and whatever Lord
told us to follow we should follow that
now we're not gonna read all of uh John
15 I mean 14 15- 22 but the one said in
there is in ver let's go read John 14
and verse 15 and then we'll come back to
Matthew okay John 14 and 15 read that if
he love me keep my Commandments if we
love God that's what we gonna do so all
of this you know love God and love your
neighbor as you do yourself whatever God
commanded you to do is what you should
be doing now let's go to Matthew 22 and
pick it up at verse
36 go go ahead Master which is the great
commandment in the law Jesus said unto
him thou shall love the Lord thy God
with all thy heart and with all thy soul
and with all thy mind this if you love
the Lord your God with all your heart
soul and mind you gonna do everything
that he tell you to do because Jes told
you
that okay go ahead this is the first and
great
commandment and the second is like unto
it Thou shalt love thy neighbor as
thyself yes sir go ahead on these two
Commandments hang all the law and the
prophets so if you love your neighbor
all those other laws that are written
you will abide in them if you love your
neighbor now let's go to one last place
Romans 13 ver
8-10 Romans 138 8 through1 go ahead when
you get it brother oh no man anything
but to love one another for he that
loveth another had fulfilled the law for
this Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not kill Thou shalt not steal Thou
shalt not bear false witness Thou shalt
not covet and if there be any other
commandment it is briefly comprehended
in the same namely Thou shalt love thy
neighbor as
thyself love worketh no ill to his
neighbor therefore love is the
fulfilling of the law so love is the
fulfilling of the law because that's
what love is built on however whatever
God tell you to do now we talking about
loving your neighbor not committing
adultery killing but whatever God say do
is what we should
do I hope that helps yeah that's right
brother Dre how can he do away with a
law that he kept himself when he came in
the flesh that's right and and and what
what do he what does it say in Romans 3
and 31 do we make void the law through
faith that's right no we establish the
law yes we do
yeah that is
correct yeah all right thank you for
that brother hope that answered their
question as we move on to our next one
my time is flying when we having fun Dev
yes next one brother Anthony horsey says
can you please share some light on
Hebrews 6 verses 1 and two what is the
meaning from repentance of dead works
and of Faith towards god let's go there
quickly brother James at Hebrews 6 read
1 and two and the guest caller we take
it from there about what is the meaning
from repentance of dead works and of
Faith towards God Hebrews 6 and verses
one and 1- two therefore leaving the
principles of the doctrine of Christ let
us go on unto Perfection not laying
again the foundation of repentance from
dead works and a faith toward God the
doctrine of baptisms and of laying on of
hands and of resurrection of the dead
and of of Eternal judgment
yes now the first thing is let exam
let's examine that first verse it says
uh uh let us go on unto Perfection not
laying again the foundation of
repentance from dead works and our faith
of Faith toward God which you mean by
not laying again the foundation of
repentance in other words don't turn
away once you done start don't start
saying it again because then you to get
salvation then you got to repent again
so when you start sining again you are
laying the
foundation and the whole thing is that
to make it clear the Lord is telling you
look once you found this thing don't
turn around and sin against it you got a
problem so let's skip down to verse four
in this same uh chapter here and we'll
get an understanding it's going to
explain itself verse four and and we're
going to read from uh uh 4 to 6 okay for
it is impossible impossible for those
who were once enlightened and have
tasted of the Heavenly gift and were
made partakers of the Holy Ghost and
have tasted
he said is impossible you know which was
made which was once enlightened that
mean that you knew the truth then yeah
have tasted the uh Heavenly gift that
mean that you have really understood
this word and you got an
understanding and were made partakers of
the Holy Ghost you was a part of the
word of God you was form so it's
impossible to to do what verse five go
ahead and have tasted the good word of
God and the powers of the world to
come if they shall fall away to renew
them again unto repentance seeing They
Crucified to themselves the Son of God
aresh and put him to an open
shame right now you done been in this
word and you got understanding and you
really saw it then all of a sudden you
turn and don't want to to deal with it
no more and you teach against it God
it's impossible to renew you why is it
impossible because you've tasted it and
you didn't like your
taste and this is what the say going to
happen to you get down and go to Hebrews
the 10th chapter read verse 26-
29 Hebrews 10: 26- 29 says for if we sin
willfully after we have received the
knowledge of the truth there remaineth
no more sacrifice for
sins but a certain fearful looking for
of judgment and fiery indignation which
shall Devour the adversaries he that he
that despised Moses's law died without
Mercy under two or three
Witnesses of how much sore punishment
suppos ye shall he be thought taught uh
worthy who hath trotten under under the
underfoot the Son of God and had counted
the blood of the Covenant wherewith he
was Sanctified and an holy thing and had
done despite unto the spirit of
Grace so the whole thing is when you
have uh come into this
word and then you decide you don't want
to deal with no more you go back into
the world that mean you laying the
foundation of repentance again that mean
you got to repent again if you you
decide to come back to the Lord because
once you have tasted the good word and
once you know about the Lord and you
aware the truth look and you turn away
from it then
willfully then only thing you have to
look forward to L A Fire that's all it's
saying of repentance to start it right
and then you decide to go wrong again
all wow I tell you fear ye him
all right our next question
sister all right next question uh read
the Bible daily uh would like for you to
explain 1 Corinthians 10 verse
24 what is another's
wealth 1 Corinthians 10 and 24 brother
Jerome what you got let's go look at it
I'm there
go ahead and read let no man seek his
own but every man another's
wealth now what I like to do is explain
what that verse is is really talking
about because if you just want to know
what another man's wealth is if that's
all you want to know you know you
talking about his assets his riches but
I I know that's not what you're really
asking you want to know what this verse
really talking about and uh Philippians
chapter 2 verse 4 and five
will explain it perfectly Philippians 2
ver 4 and 5
yeah look not every man on his own
things but every man also on the things
of others yeah let let this mind be in
you which was also in Christ Jesus yeah
that's all I got on
you all right hope that answer that
question brother as we move on moving on
Sam Burns
um yeah Sam Burns ask is the scripture
and the law the same Julia it's the
scripture and the
law come off mute
brother my apologies uh yes uh the law
we hung up on the word law which is
commonly called the first five books of
Moses um which is Genesis Exodus
Leviticus Numbers and Deuteronomy which
is which is called the law but really
it's scripture and the definition of
scripture is the sacred writings of the
Old and New Testament that is the true
definition of scripture the sacred
writings of the Old and New Testaments
let's go to Luke the 24th chapter and
let's give you an a beautiful example a
beautiful example that the Lord left us
Luke 24 brother
James we going to read verses 25- 27 pay
attention to how this is written because
these words are contained scripture and
law is
interchangeable then he said unto them
oh fools I'm sorry verse 27 verse 27
Luke 2427 go ahead and beginning at
Moses and all the prophets he EXP
founded unto them in all the scriptures
the things concerning himself now Moses
is what is in the first five books he
wrote the first five books right but
they call it the law but yet it is
scripture notice how those two words is
there uh so the law is there and the
scriptures is there skip down uh
continue uh uh skip down my brother to
verse uh let's see skip up to verse 25
20 go up to 25 go ahead then he said
unto them oh fools and slow of heart to
believe all that the prophets have
spoken uhhuh ought not Christ to have
suffered these things and to enter into
his glory so now Jesus is referring back
to that which is written in the Old
Testament now the first half of 27 go
ahead and beginning at Moses and all the
prophets go ahead he expounded unto them
in all the scriptures the things
concerning himself that's Malachi to
Revelation that that's the rest of it
but it's all scripture give me verse 44
go
ahead and he said unto them these are
the words which I spake unto you while I
was yet with you that all things must be
fulfilled which were written in the law
of Moses and in the prophets and in the
Psalms concerning me so he went all the
way to the Psalms he went all the way to
the psalms now let's go to One Last
Place St John the 10th chapter brother
James St John 10 and we gonna pick this
up at 34 and 35 and we'll be done with
that okay St John 10 34 and 35 go ahead
Jesus answered them is it not written in
your law I said ye are God now that's
Psalms 82 in the Old Testament which is
still scripture go ahead if he called
them Gods unto whom the word of God came
and the scripture cannot be broken he
called the Psalms the
scriptures so the words are
interchangeable but man gets hooked up
on the words like the law which is what
we call the Torah which is nothing but
the teachings and instruction and the
doctrine which is the whole Bible I hope
that
helped sir thank you hope that answered
the question question as time is running
out on us let's see if we can panel and
speed round a couple of these few
questions here sister deah what's the
next okay the next one Barbie Reed says
I took a part-time job on the
weekend Friday Saturday and Sunday to
make ends me I read Hebrews 10 verse 26
and got scared should I
quit all right that Hebrews 10:2 6 if I
sin willfully after I received the
knowledge of God but they want to know
because they working on the weekend
Friday Saturday and Sunday hey should
they quit their job if they are making
ends
me well the week ends
Sunday okay but my question is it's a
part-time job and a lot of times they'll
let you they allow you to make your
schedule so can you work
Friday can you be all the Sabbath and
can you work
Sunday mhm that's just my take over it
yeah or or Saturday after the Sabbath is
over right brother yes sir if possible
yeah so all right that's all we got on
that one next
question all right client says I was
told that Jesus hidden name is Israel
and the Holy Spirit is teaching this now
is this true and can you provide
scripture that says
this look to the
panel
hidden Jesus name was Israel we was
Israel okay let's go I Isaiah the 49th
chapter all
right okay Isaiah
49 uh make sure start reading it PR so I
want to make sure either 49 or 59 start
reading the 49 and see what it
says listen all AES unto me and hearken
ye people from afar the Lord had called
me from the womb from the vows of my
mother ha he made mention of my
name and he had made and he have made my
mouth like a sharp sword in the shadow
of his hand have he hid me and made me a
Polish shaft in his quiver had he hid me
now see this is Jesus that's why he see
made his mouth was sh's SW so and but go
go ahead and read and said unto me thou
art my servant o Israel in whom I will
be
glorified now he is not talking about
the people he is talking about Jesus he
said thou my servant o Israel in whom I
will be glorified he read then I said I
have labored in vain I have spent my
strength for not and in vain yet surely
my judgment is with the Lord and my work
with
God uhuh and now sayth the Lord that
formed me from the womb to be his
servant to bring Jacob again to him
though through though Israel be not
gathered yet shall I be glorious in the
eyes of the Lord and my God shall be my
strength goad and he said it is a light
thing that thou should us be my servant
to raise up the tribes of Jacob and to
restore the preserved of Israel I will
also give thee for a light to the
Gentiles that thou mayest be my
salvation until the end of the Earth so
this is Jesus is the one that the Lord
called uh that uh uh was named Israel
and he was the one that the Lord sent to
recover Israel and also be a light to
the Gentiles that his salvation will be
to the ends of the Earth so Jesus
adopted Jacob and gave Jacob his name
Israel that's why he's called The Holy
he's called the father also in Isaiah
the uh uh uh ninth chapter okay so it's
Israel here isra Israel is Jesus name
one of Jesus and when he adopted Jacob
he called Jacob by his name like what
that's what you do when you adopt a
child you don't let them keep their own
name you give them your name so no the
name Israel the first one named Israel
was Jesus don't have to say all right so
sister debah let's do this final
question no scripture NE necessary they
just want to know can you uh ask that
question please all right uh the next
question you're right is it okay Janie
doe says is it okay for Christian
stalkers and cashier to display or sell
holiday based products such as
decorations and Christmas lights some
employers will not accommodate for such
religious exemption if they create
financial
burden all right so looks like this
question here they saying that they work
as a cashier or stalker and people
buying Christmas lights and decorations
and the job won't give it off and they
have to work that time so they want to
know is that creating a
problem no it's not you that's just a
job to you all that that's it yep that's
it so we're going to leave leave that
right there and sister Deborah time
check yes the time is
9:04 we have ran out of time we want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who tuned in with us we had a good
time with you this evening if you
submitted a question we didn't have a
chance to get to it please don't
resubmit it sister Deborah take your
question put it in rotation and we will
deal with your question next Wednesday
so until we all come together again
please be safe out there be blessed BL
may the Lord have mercy on us all as
brother James closes us out Our Father
which art in heaven Hallowed be thy name
thy kingdom come thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven give us this
day our daily bread and forgive us our
debts as we forgive our debors and lead
us not into temptation but Deliver Us
from Evil for thine is the kingdom and
the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen amen amen good night all good
night everybody